adonly.com 2017-04-11

# Privacy Policy | AdOnly

AdOnly, as part of providing online services, we collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, Password.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

AdOnly takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our customers and ensures that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the customer's consent. AdOnly has numerous security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of our customer's information. All customer information is password protected and only accessible by authorized members of the AdOnly staff.

However, there may be times when AdOnly may be required to disclose personal information of a customer without his/her express consent when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the customer.

While AdOnly , our associates and affiliates make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither we nor you will know.

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to our terms and conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by our terms, we politely ask that you do not use this.

Loading, please wait...
